this world is
hey what is going on here this world this world is being closed up
all because of my magic
we're leaving this place come on fight no we can't all go however
don't let go of sakura and mokuna what do you have up your sleeve you need to leave now
are you okay
i can't find magic
hey charan what mokuna the ring that's always in mokuna's ear take it
i learned about it in a dream it was from the other mokuna please do it
go
oh
Oh, my God.
覚えている 日の光で
小鳥のように 目覚めた日を
未来なんて 当たり前に
来るものだと思っていた
好きな人とずっと 一緒にいたい
そんな単純な夢も 叶えられずに
僕らはここで 離れてしまうの
早く 一番大切な人のところへ
このまま 君を本当に失う
その前に 答えは特に 決まってる
想いを 形に変えるんだ
時代だ
Where am I?
Anybody?
This is Japan.
Princess Tomoyo.
Is that you?
It's good to see you again, Kurokane.
And the voice I heard before?
Yes, that was me.
Go.
If you truly wish him to come with you, you must sacrifice something with the same magical
power in exchange.
When you heard that, you were moments from death, wounded beyond what my Shu curse could
heal.
People dream before they die.
Even a warrior like you.
So you entered my dream, and you told me how to bring him out.
With that spell, its caster must first become its core for it to work.
And so, the caster may not ever leave that place.
He must remain to hold the spell.
He had used up almost all of his magical power to allow the rest of you to escape.
He cast a spell on my left arm.
I assumed that by leaving it behind, I allowed him to escape.
Now, do you understand what true strength is?
Maybe.
Though in the process, I seem to have lost some of mine.
I killed a man.
Did you already know that, too, from your dreaming?
Did you know that this would happen because I took another's life?
I had hoped that, in the end, it wouldn't.
You called it a curse.
Is that why?
Aren't you going to ask me why I didn't tell you in the first place?
Knowledge without the ability to speak.
A pain only those who have had it know.
What good would it do me to blame you for the pain that you've endured?
Karogini.
It's all right.
I don't have any regrets whatsoever about losing my arm back there.
All my life, I've hungered for power.
So that no one would ever hurt what was dear to me again.
However, even power itself can bring pain.
And besides, there are things that power cannot protect.
I'm so proud of you.
You've finally learned what true strength is.
Thank you for waiting patiently.
Now, please, enter the room.
Kind, sir.
What is it?
That was for earlier, Kurger Burger.
I'll get you for that.
Just wait.
Yes, I understand.
Now, be on your way.
Don't disappear.
Don't disappear, other one.
Sharon!
Good morning!
How do you feel?
Are you still hurting anywhere?
I'm fine.
Thanks for asking, Mokuna.
Sakura?
And Sakura?
What is this?
Sakura?
I took it upon myself to treat her injuries.
Thank you, Tomoyo.
But why is she up in a tree?
This tree is the oldest of its kind in all of Japan.
Its Sakura, or cherry blossoms, will help her, even if her body is without a soul.
This tree has your name, Sakura.
I see you've returned, Kurogane.
Yeah?
You should not address her so informally.
It seems you've improved a little since you were with us last.
Huh?
I welcome the other visitors as well.
May you find peace within this castle.
I know your journey must continue.
We have another guest.
Fuma, hi!
Well, long time no see, little one.
Although I suppose I really shouldn't assume that time is flow to the same pace for both of us.
That would be foolish.
So have you come to Japan to search for something, Fuma?
No.
I just have something to deliver.
Hey, uh, what is that?
It's a prosthetic arm.
I didn't have time to create skin for it, so I apologize for its appearance.
I thought you would want it as soon as it was done.
But why are you bringing this to me?
And how may I ask, do you even know about this?
Yuko filled me in on what had happened.
Yuko did?
Yes, that's right.
She asked me to deliver this to you.
I came by it in another world.
One that's far more technologically advanced than this.
A country called Piffle.
What's the price?
Well, actually, Yuko already compensated me.
Oh, and speaking of Yuko...
I took the liberty of promising the payment that she required.
I'm afraid you were asleep at the time, Kuro.
Bye, your eye color changed!
The secret was in my blue eyes.
They're what gave me my magic power.
Mokona, will you take this to the witch?
But why?
Don't worry about me.
I can still see just fine.
This is just the last remaining bit of my magical ability.
Don't do it!
You can't lose your magic!
You'll die!
No, I won't die.
The vampire blood I received will keep me alive for now.
It's all right, Mokona.
I wouldn't be willing to throw away my life as easily as that...
anymore.
Okay, Fai.
I'll send it to Yuko now.
So it's arrived, then.
And now there's only one more to go.
Not bad at all.
I think I like you better this way.
Oh, shut up.
Well, we're cold.
Oh, let's go!
You're престil!
Shujiro!
Say, Shiro!
How long has it been, I wonder?
It's hard to know for sure, I suppose.
Who can tell if time flows the same for all of us?
That's almost exactly what you said, Fuma.
Is that because he's your big brother?
Well, it's a bit more complicated than that.
You're the same as ever, aren't you, brother?
Same to you.
Though looking at the two of you, I can't repeat the sentiment.
It seems to me that you've both changed, dramatically.
Especially you, magician.
You've lost all your magical powers, haven't you?
But gained a vampire's blood.
Oh, no!
It's Kamui's blood, isn't it?
And if it is, what then?
Where are they?
Both of them, Kamui and Tsubara.
So, this is your older brother?
Yeah, and he's quite a handful.
Just like my sister.
Hmm?
And what do you mean by that?
I'm sure she was only kidding, weren't you, princess?
There are better ways of asking someone a question, don't you think?
Look who's talking.
Shut up!
He is right, you know.
Yes!
I don't remember asking for a second opinion!
So sorry.
Why don't I try again?
If I'm not mistaken, you met the twin vampires.
I met them both while in a different world.
It was in Tokyo.
And now, are they still in Tokyo?
Not now.
They've moved on.
But that was after all of these guys left.
Where to?
You think they would tell me I'm your younger brother, after all?
Well, they say that hunters are supposed to be drawn to their quarry.
But no matter what methods I use, I can't seem to be able to find my prey.
Hmm.
Well, I'll be off to the next world, then.
Wait!
What have we here, another Shauron?
What happened to the feather?
I have it.
Right here.
Give it to me.
It was the land of Oto.
No, wait.
It was actually Idunas' country, wasn't it?
That's where I found it.
And naturally, I took it with me.
It has the power to turn the imaginary into reality.
And you think I'll hand it over?
That I'll just give it to you without a fight?
Give it back.
It appears you're prepared for the alternative, then.
I've been watching you for a long time.
I know who you are.
Watching me through the eyes of another you?
Yes.
You're just like your father.
But that's not surprising, I suppose.
Blood will always tell in the end, won't it?
Well, then.
Wait a moment!
I cannot allow you to fight like this.
You will destroy the castle.
What is this?
It looks like a barrier.
An alternate dimension.
Yes, I'd say that's a barrier, all right.
We can be as reckless as we please here.
And our actions won't affect the space in reality.
However, any wounds we inflict will follow us back there.
All right.
Let us begin.
Where am I?
Sakura, it's you.
I don't understand.
You know me?
I wouldn't say I know you exactly.
We met at Yuko's shop.
Oh, but you were asleep at that point, I guess.
Where are we?
Is this the inside of our shop?
No, that's not it.
Maybe, maybe this is a dream.
I think you're right.
We must be trapped within a dream.
We should have Kurogane and my sister watch their fight to its final conclusion.
I can tell that there's something you would like to speak with me about, Fi.
From what I've been told, you're a dream watcher, aren't you?
So then you're able to tell the future through dreams.
But then, the first time that we encountered each other in Japan.
Hurry, he's dying.
If he dies, if he dies, then I'll...
It's all right.
Kurogane is not going to die.
I didn't sense it then.
The power of the dream watcher.
How do you explain that?
You and I have something in common.
I gave it to Yuko as payment as well.
I gave her my power.
And what were you paying for?
Was that the compensation Yuko asked for to bring us all here?
Those of us who can read the future are limited.
We can do nothing but see what lies ahead.
But still we hope.
And we wish that our loved ones choose to walk the happiest path possible.
Unfortunately, there's precious little else that we can do.
But you know that.
It's much like your king.
So I'm assuming that you know all about King Asherah.
Yes.
The king was constantly looking into the future.
Trying to see if there was some small way to save you.
While he was falling apart.
However, changing what we see is very difficult.
Even the slightest word or movement or emotion, any one of these things,
they can alter the course of the future.
And the change is irreversible.
It's like tiny ripples in the water that are forever multiplying.
Princess Sakura.
She knew as well.
Which is why she couldn't tell you anything of use.
There were always certain warning signs.
A number of things about the king's behavior that I found unreasonable.
And I think it's because...
Reason is crumbling.
Soon it may disappear.
For the sake of Fei Wang Reed's dream.
Oh yes.
The shattering of reason is just what he wants.
Indeed.
He wants it more than anything.
A very understandable wish.
But reason itself is a natural law that no one can overturn.
Then his desire is not unlike my own.
To bring back someone who's already dead.
Sha'ron!
Sha'ron, no!
You can't help him.
But I have to!
Sha'ron is going to die!
All right, then.
I'll be going now.
Not so fast!
You can't go. It isn't over yet.
Apparently not.
No matter what, I will get the feather back.
Thunder!
Emperor!
That sucker is feather.
That attack came a little too close for comfort.
I said give it back!
No!
Hey, kid, look out!
Shaoran, no!
Shaoran!
Now come back with her!
We're there!
Tell me, what's your name?
What's your name?
Watanuki.
It means April 1st.
April 1st?
That's the day Shaoran and I were born.
You're born.
Huh?
Look out, Sakura!
ohnehin'.
Oh, it's the day hour it was fatal, must I make money?
Ugh.
Ugh...
Ah...
Huh?
Ooh!
Ah...
You're not gonna fall.
Thank you.